MD. TAMIM HASAN



Software Engineer Major in Data Science

CONTACT

mrtamimrasel5@gmail.com

+8801300306993

Phanmondi32, Dhaka 1207

ramlit limited

@RSTamim

in MR Tamim

SKILLS

Programming

JAVA JavaScript ES6

ReactJS JQuery

WordPress HTML/CSS

PlugIn MySQL

Photoshop

Illustrator Adobe XD

Operating Systems

MacOS Windows

Another skill
Problem Solving

Prog. Competition Team Work

Languages

Bengal English Hindi



CERTIFICATES

Bachelor Degree Data Science Summit Programming Contest Google Search Contest

ABOUT THIS TEMPLATE

Hard-working professional with almost 2 year of experience and a proven knowledge of service delivery, order processing and customer satisfaction. Aiming to leverage my skill to successfully file the Font End Developer role at your company. Demonstrated talent for front and back-end web development.

WORK HISTORY

₩ 04/2021-current

Ramlit Limited
 Dhaka, Dhaka Bangladesh
 A full stack developer at ramlit limited.

Web Developer

m 01/2022-current

SeoPage1

Dhaka,Dhaka Bangladesh

Web Developer

A web developer and web development trainee at SeoPage1

EDUCATION

1 01/2018 - 02/2022

Q Daffodil International University, Dhaka

Bachelor of Software Engineer

1 05/2014 - 03/2017

Shahdowla Govt Collage, Rajshahi

Higher Secondary Education

ACHIEVEMENTS, HONOURS AND AWARDS

Data Science Summit,4th position

Programming Competition inter Dept.

GENERAL SKILLS

Web Design | Web Development

Graphic Design

UI/UX design

Microsoft

Proftfolio Design

I love to learn new think everyday. I love team work. I also continuously try to improve my skill.

WHEEL CHART

